standardfiber.com 2004-12-07

# coaxial cable, rf connectors, rf cables

**RF COAX INC. Privacy Policy Statement**

RF COAX INC. is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the RF COAX web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

The RF COAX web site collects information in several ways. Currently this is limited to Requests for Quotation and E-Mail inquiries. 

Some personal information is gathered when you request a quotation. During the quote process, we ask for your name, title, organization, and email address. The system will also ask for your street address, telephone, and Fax number. In addition to personal information, the quote form asks you for product information that may be proprietary.

No cookies are utilized.

The primary goal of the RF COAX web site in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized quotation and/or to respond to your inquiries. Ultimately, our objective is to provide a solution to your RF cable needs. 

When you are asked for personal information by the RF COAX web site, you are sharing that information with RF COAX alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise.

As a general rule, RF COAX INC. will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. RF COAX INC. may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of RF COAX INC., other users of the RF COAX web site or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. RF COAX INC. may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. 

If you choose not to submit a Request for Quotation or E-Mail providing personal information, you can still use most of the RF COAX web site. 

RF COAX INC. does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, RF COAX INC. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

RFCOAX.COM is a commercial web site. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. RF COAX INC. does not share personal information about users under the age of 18 with third parties and we do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of age. In addition, RF COAX INC. will not send any direct email offers to users who indicate they are under the age of 18. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example in quotes that you submit or through email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you submit personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

Thank You - RF COAX INC.

RF COAX™ is a trademark of RF COAX INC. K Connector®, V Connector®, and W Connector® are registered trademarks of Anritsu Company. GPO & GPPO® are registered trademarks of Corning Gilbert. All trademarks are the property of their respective owners. US COAX  [uscoax.com](http://www.uscoax.com/), Digital Coax [digitalcoax.com](http://www.digitalcoax.com/), Standard Fiber [standardfiber.com](http://www.standardfiber.com/), [phasematch.com](http://www.phasematch.com/), [labwave.com](http://www.labwave.com/), [etherstate.com](http://www.etherstate.com/), [mediapayload.com](http://www.mediapayload.com/), [rfinput.com](http://www.rfinput.com/), [rfoutput.com](http://www.rfoutput.com/), [0dBm.com](http://www.0dbm.com/), [returnloss.com](http://www.returnloss.com/), [insertionloss.com](http://www.insertionloss.com/), [inputmatch.com](http://www.inputmatch.com/), [outputmatch.com](http://www.outputmatch.com/), [reflectioncoefficient.com](http://www.reflectioncoefficient.com/), [and s-parameter.com](http://www.and%20s-parameter.com/), are associated with RF COAX INC... _Discover the Solution_... [discoverthesolution.com](http://www.discoverthesolution.com/)
